Hello.
Managing complex deals in HubSpot can
quickly become messy.
We often have many contacts, notes, and
meetings.
All of this is recorded in the CRM.
But it's still hard to answer one simple
question:
who actually matters in this account?
Who is the decision maker?
Who is the champion?
Who is blocking the deal?
This is where org charts come in.
Org charts provide the visual layer that
HubSpot does not offer natively.
With org charts, we can just edit the
org chart, and if we don't have any
yet, we can generate it with AI.
The AI will take all the recorded
information about meetings, calls, and
notes and it will create the best
organizational chart for this deal and
this company, according to the records.
We can also organize it in a very simple
drag and drop editor and then adjust it
to our needs.
It's also possible to have different
buying roles.
These buying roles are custom, and we
can decide who is an important contact
for the buying committee.
When that is done, the org chart will
appear directly on the record, so it's
very easy to visualize.
We have direct access to the org chart
from the record.
It's also available from companies and
contacts records.
From the company page, we can see all
the org charts related to this
particular company.
We can also have different org charts
for every deal.
There is also the possibility to
visualize all the org charts for the
account or the organisation in a
central location.
With org charts, it is super easy to
manage stakeholders, manage
relationships, reporting lines, or
buying roles, and help close these
complex deals with lot of information
scattered across many different
records..
It is very easy to install.
It's available in the marketplace , so
go ahead and try org chart today.
No credit card required to test for the
first 5 charts you create, and, after,
you can continue with a 30-day free
trial.
Thank you.